Oh, my Go... Hang it. Wow. Um...
You know, l'd have to get a hook
and nails and a hammer, and...
- No problem.
- Oh, look.
You've got... You just...
You got it all right there. Wow.
l found him. He's in the bathroom.
- President Seibert?
- Can't this wait?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, we just need a word.
(Siebert:)Now? You realize I'm your boss
and I am holding my penis.
Sheldon, give the man some privacy.
I'm sorry, this guy's got no respect
for boundaries.
(Siebert:)What do you want?
Will you tell this lunatic
that Rothman's office is mine?
(Siebert:)Take this up with your
department chairman.
(Sheldon:)His assistant said
he was on sabbatical.
AIthough, we distinctly heard
his office window open and shut.
(Siebert:)Gentlemen, there's a task
I'm trying to accomplish here...
(Siebert:)- ...and I'm having trouble doing it.
- Oh, my.
President Seibert,
I don't mean to be an alarmist...
...but difficuIty initiating
a urine stream...